字幕组
ZiMuZu.tv
我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来  我只是个普通的鉴证专员
To the outside world, I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
but secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
在我打败极速并拯救了多元宇宙后
After defeating Zoom and saving the multiverse,
我跑回到了过去
I ran back in time
创造出了另一条时间线  闪点
and created the alternate timeline, Flashpoint.
我恢复了时间线原来的状态
I restored the timeline to how it was,
但发现有些事却不一样了
only to find things weren't as I left them.
我给我们的世界带来了新的威胁
I brought new threats to our world,
而我是唯一来得及阻止他们的人
and I'm the only one fast enough to stop them.
我就是  闪电侠
I am The Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
他们没发现你的潜力
They don't see your potential.
-我发现了  -你想接受训练吗
- I do. - You want to train?
我来训练你
I'll train you.
你是艾伦的朋友  斯诺博士
You're Allen's friend, Dr. Snow.
我求你不要揭发她
I'm begging you, don't turn her in.
你要我做什么都可以
I will do anything you want.
你马上就去递交辞呈
Tender your resignation, effective immediately.
闪电侠在危机中消失
这报道原本是爱瑞丝·韦斯特·艾伦写的
It's a story--it used to be written by Iris West-Allen.
由朱莉·格里尔撰写
我们的未来有所改变了
Something's changed with our future.
-天呐  我做了什么  -我哥哥死了
- God, what did I do? - My brother's dead.
我没法再拥有跟丹堤一起的记忆了
Now I'll never make another memory with Dante again.
你只是一介凡人  闪电侠
You're only a man, Flash.
而我是神
But I am a god.
我是萨维塔
I am Savitar.
现在我们知道炼金术师只是跟班
Now we know Alchemy's just a lackey.
朱利安  再一次成为我的仆人
Julian, become my servant once more.
成为炼金术师
Become Alchemy.
印度河流域
四年前
我到印度已经半年了
It's been six months since I arrived here in India.
尽管我心怀信仰
Though I have faith it's out there,
但驱使我至此的声音已逐渐衰弱
the voice that once drove me has waned.
我担心我的探寻会是徒劳一场
And I fear my quest may be for naught.
朱利安  快过来
Julian, come quick.
我觉得我们找到它了
I think we found it.
就是这个  帮我照清楚
This is it. Here, hold this.
就是它了
This is it.
我能感觉到
I can feel it.
我觉得应该等等再打开它
I think we should wait before we open it.
它需要重获自由
It needs to be set free.
闪电侠
第三季
第九集
神圣的《冬季仙境》
Holy winter wonderland.
冬天的圣诞颂歌  被视为一个圣诞节流行标准
让我不禁脱口而出
Took the words right out of my mouth.
看来地球19的圣诞节和我们的差不多
Well, I guess Earth-19's Christmas is just like ours.
有些传统是共通的
Some traditions are multi-versal.
对了...
So, um...
有萨维塔的消息吗
any more info on Savitar?
没有  我们只知道他是极速之神
Nope, all the we know is that he's a speed god
还有你是唯一可以看到他的人
and you're the only one who can see him.
炼金术师是萨维塔的大祭司
All right, well, Alchemy is Savitar's high priest
他的超能力来源于那块用于创造超能力者
and he gets his power from the stone
的石头  所以我觉得
that he uses to create meta, so I was thinking
如果我们能发现那石头是什么
if we can find out what that thing is,
也许就有办法阻止他
maybe we can figure out how to stop him.
我去看看能不能查到些什么
I want to see if I can dig something up.
好的
Okay.
我知道这是我们在一起后的第一个圣诞节
I know this is our first Christmas together as a couple
我想让一切完美  但...
and I want everything to be perfect, but...
你得去做这件事
You need to get to this.
是的  我完全理解
Yes--no, I totally get it.
我查到了牛津大学一个关于
I got a dissertation here from Oxford University
古印度神话武器的论文
about the myth of an ancient Hindu weapon
叫作梵天法宝
called the Brahmastra.
拥有惊人超能力的传奇石器
Legendary artifact with incredible powers,
能够  等等
capable of--wait for it--
创造出超能力者
Creating metas.
Creating meta-humans.
大伙们  这和炼金术师的石头很像
Guys, that looks just like Alchemy's stone.
更重要的是...
More importantly...
看这论文是谁写的
look who wrote this paper.
作者  艾伯特·戴斯蒙德
朱利安
Julian?
你把这儿收拾得不错
Love what you've done with the place.
艾伦
Allen.
我们不是说好了吗
Thought we had a deal.
我为你的冰霜朋友保守秘密
I keep your frosty friend's secret,
而你不能再踏进这扇门  记得吗
and you never darken these doors again, remember?
我只是想问你一些关于炼金术师
I just need some information from you
用的石头的信息
about that stone that Alchemy uses.
为什么要问我
And you've come to me because?
印度流域的神器之谜
作者艾伯特·戴斯蒙德
显然你对此很了解
Apparently, you know a lot about it.
不如你把知道的一切告诉我吧
Well, why don't you tell me everything you know?
然后我就不再烦你了
And you'll never hear from me again.
好吧
Fine.
许多年前  我听说梵天法宝
Many years ago, I heard about the Brahmastra,
或俗称为
or as it's colloquially called,
魔法石
the Philosopher's Stone.
据说是第一件能赋予人类超能力的宝物
It is said to be the first object to give human beings powers.
就像粒子加速器
Like the Particle Accelerator.
很多年来  它遗失了
Over the years, it got lost.
我痴迷于找寻这件宝物
I became quite obsessed with trying to find it.
我做了每一个相关的研究
Did every piece of available research I could
并且利用未来将继承的遗产
and much to my parents' dismay,
资助了一队探险队去寻找
I used my future inheritance
我父母对此很失望
and funded an expedition to try and find it.
可是我们从未找到
But we never found it.
在那之后不久  我回到了这里
Pretty soon after that, I came here.
恕我失陪了  我有工作要做
Now, if you'll excuse me, I have work to do.
在你的研究中  你是否听过
In your research, have you ever come across
萨维塔这个名字
the name Savitar?
你怎么知道这个名字的
How do you know that name?
我自己也做了一些研究
I've done some research of my own.
据我所知
As far as I know,
萨维塔是第一个有神速力的超能力者
Savitar is the first meta with speed.
我知道的就这么多  艾伦
That's all I know, Allen.
我建议别在这上面浪费时间
And I suggest that you don't waste your time on this.
你走吧
Move on.
好
All right.
朱利安
Julian.
中城警局
给
Here you go.
外星人一出动  所有怪事都一起来了
One whiff of aliens and all the crazies come out.
我要埋在这堆外星人资料
I'm gonna be buried under these alien files
直到明年圣诞节了
until next Christmas.
如果有圣诞奇迹
Well, if by some Christmas miracle
你就早点从堆里爬出来
you dig yourself out sooner,
去韦斯特家边过平安夜  边弄这堆文件吧
we do it up at the West house on Christmas Eve.
有火鸡  圣诞树  埃丝特祖母的蛋酒
Turkey, tree, Grandma Esther's eggnog,
还有这堆工作  我们希望你能来
the whole shebang-- and we would love for you to come.
只有一个条件  我自带蛋酒
One condition: I bring the nog.
我米莉祖母的食谱  肯定会让你们大吃一惊
My Grandma Millie's recipe, it is gonna knock your socks off.
等一下
Oh, wait a minute.
我们来一场蛋酒对决吧
We gonna have a little nog-off.
不是吧
Really?
埃丝特祖母对战米莉祖母
Grandma Esther versus Grandma Millie.
你知道我喜欢挑战  乔·韦斯特
Oh, you know I love a challenge, Joe West.
愿最棒的祖母胜出
May the best grandma win.
我替你的祖母感到惋惜
I am so sorry for your grandma.
等着瞧吧
We'll see.
-好  我来接你  -圣诞奇迹
- Fine. I'll pick you up, all right? - Christmas miracle.
地球三
我告诉里面的每一个人  若听从指示
I told everyone inside I'd let them live
我就让他们活命
if they followed instructions.
但是我骗了他们
But I tricked them.
实在太有我的风格了
Which is so me.
放弃吧  魔术师
Give it up, Trickster!
你好啊  飞毛腿
Hiya, Swiftie.
不如赏个脸让我杀了你吧
Will you do me the honor of allowing me to kill you?
你没子弹了
You're out of ammo.
但是我还有炸弹
But I'm not out of bombs.
我们一起去来世怎么样  大个子
What do you say we take in the afterlife, big boy?
-来得正是时候  -不客气
- Nice timing. - You're welcome.
我的眼睛有毛病了
There's something wrong with my eyes.
我看东西有重影
I'm seeing double.
闪电侠暴打了我一顿
The Flash hit me too hard!
我要告你  你个飞碟脑袋
I'm gonna sue you, saucer-head!
总有一天  那个头盔会成为我的囊中之物
One day, I'll own that helmet,
然后我会用它来做烟灰缸  或糖果盘
and I'll use it as an ashtray or a candy dish.
不  等等  用来做轮毂罩
No, wait, a hubcap!
一切局面都在我掌控内  小子
I had that, kid.
那是我一直以来的口头禅
That's what I always say.
放开我
Let me go.
尤其是我以前事情搞不定的时候
Especially when I didn't have it.
我猜你大老远来到地球三  不是为了帮我
So I'm assuming you didn't come all the way to Earth-3
阻止我这边的魔术师的吧
to stop my Trickster.
我有事和你说
I have something I need to talk to you about.
有名极速者
A speedster.
自称萨维塔
Calls himself Savitar.
-萨维塔  -是的
- So... Savitar. - Yeah.
显然  你已经变得足够强大
Apparently, you've grown powerful enough
可以挑战他了
to challenge him.
他是什么人
Who is he?
不知道  从没见过他
Don't know, never seen him.
你是我认识的第一个见过他的极速者
You're the first speedster I know of who has.
但是每一个我听过有关萨维塔的故事
But every story I ever heard about Savitar
基本都一样
is basically the same.
萨维塔是第一个被赐予神速力的人
Savitar was the first man ever granted speed.
久而久之  他成为了移动之神
And over time, he became the god of motion,
是我们中速度最快的一个
the fastest of us all.
在萨维塔降临一个地球之前
Before Savitar graces an Earth with his presence...
他会派前一任来为他的到来做准备
He sends a predecessor to prepare for his arrival.
炼金术师
Alchemy.
他在做什么的准备
What's he preparing for?
与你的对决
A battle with you.
为什么是我
Why me?
你是对他力量的威胁
You're threatening his power.
你怎么知道这些的
How do you know all this?
神速力的神话  传奇  传言
Speed Force myths, legends, rumors.
如果萨维塔来找过你一次
If Savitar's come for you once,
他会再来的
he'll be back.
那时我会准备好
Then I'll be ready.
我们会准备好
We'll be ready.
跑吧  华莱士  快跑
Run! Wallace, run!
你得向左转身
You got to torque to the left!
-我成绩如何  -你成绩如何
- How'd I do? - How'd you do?
我不知道  不如你自己看看吧
Oh, I don't know, why don't you see for yourself.
等等  你是说我比巴里还快了吗
Hold up, are you saying I'm faster than Barry?
我是说与他接受训练的这个节点相比
I'm saying that at this point in his training,
你比巴里快
you're faster than Barry.
你比巴里快  你比巴里快
You're faster than Barry, you're faster than Barry,
你比巴里快
you're faster than Barry!
-我们得告诉所有人  -不是个好主意
- We got to tell everyone. - Not a good idea.
-为什么不行  -基本上是自我保护
- Why not? - Self-preservation, basically.
听着  华莱士  你有着很大的潜力
Look, Wallace, you have tremendous potential.
是的  显然  但在我来到这地球后
Yes, clearly, but one thing I've learned
学到的一件事就是  不要轻慢
since coming to this Earth is you do not trifle
韦斯特一家
with the West household.
你知道的  说你同意我
No, you know-no, say you're with me.
-我同意你  -太好了
- Yeah, I'm with you. - Yeah!
现在  我们要锻炼你的  你的躲避
Now, we're gonna work on your--your--yeah, your dodging
还有你的摆臂
and your weaving.
我读了所有印度关于神话的
I've read every Hindu textbook there is on mythology
关于鬼神和半神的教科书  什么都没有
and spirits and demigods and nothing.
没有提到过萨维塔  一次也没有
No mention of Savitar, not once.
以我的经验  答案总是会随着时间揭晓
In my experience, the answers usually tend to come in time.
是啊  我不能就坐在这里
Yeah, I can't just sit back
等着萨维塔或是炼金术师袭击
and wait for Savitar or Alchemy to attack.
你不能总是担心可能发生的未来
You can't worry about what may or may not lie ahead.
再说
Besides...
现在是圣诞节
it's Christmas.
是与你关心的人欢聚的时刻
A time to be with the ones you care about.
你知道  就只是萨维塔还没被打败
You know, it's just, Savitar's still out there.
是  但不是现在
Yeah, but not right now.
你美丽的女朋友才是重点
And your beautiful girlfriend is.
把你的脑袋从那些书中拉出来
Get your head out of the books
回到你的生活中  与你所爱的人相处
and back into your life with your loved ones
趁你现在还拥有他们
while you have them.
杰伊认为他想出了找到石头的办法
Hey, Jay thinks he figured out a way to find the stone.
你没事吧
You okay?
我不知道
I don't know.
我一直看到我哥哥
I keep seeing my brother.
这里到处都是  在控制室也是
Everywhere-here, in the cortex...
这是丹堤死后你的第一个圣诞节
Well, this is your first Christmas since Dante died.
也许是你的大脑在捉弄你
Maybe your mind's playing tricks on you.
是啊
Yeah.
也许吧
Probably.
曾有那么一次圣诞节  一大家子团聚
There was this one Christmas, big family affair.
而丹堤和我  你知道的
and Dante and I, you know,
我们小时候经常打架
we used to fight all the time as kids,
但是那一个圣诞节
but that one Christmas,
我们没有打架
we didn't fight.
我们就坐在那里喝酒聊天
We just sat and we talked and we drank
一整瓶的威士忌  然后...
a whole bottle of whiskey, and...
那一整晚  我们都在笑
that whole night, we were laughing.
那真是...
It's...
而就那一晚
And that one night--
那一晚  我们有了兄弟的感觉
that one night, it was like we felt like brothers.
我爸爸死前的那个圣诞节
The last Christmas before my dad died,
下了很久很久的雪
it snowed and snowed.
他和我就坐在屋里  看老电影
He and I just sat inside, watching old movies
任由外边的世界变成白色
while the whole world turned white.
简直是梦幻一般
It was magical.
咱们今年就只谈扫兴的事吗
Are we about to be the Grinches this year?
你这克制力真不错
Nice use of restraint.
是啊  我采购之后
Yeah, well, I shopped,
又采购  现在
and I shopped, and now,
我准备好躺到你的怀里了
I am ready to drop into your arms.
抱歉我错过了和你一起圣诞节采购
I'm sorry I missed Christmas shopping with you.
没事  我买了一切必需品
It's okay. I have everything I need.
所以你对给我礼物有像
So are you as excited to give me my present
我给你礼物那样期待吗
as I am to give you yours?
那当然
Yeah, of course.
肯定的  没错
Definitely. Yeah.
你是买了礼物的  对吧
You did get me something, right?
我是给你买了
I did get you something, yeah.
我就是  还没有打包呢
I just--I haven't wrapped it yet, is all.
-好吧  -好吧
- Okay. - Okay.
对了  还有  在你告诉我关于
Okay, um, by the way, after you told me about
朱利安的考古研究后
Julian's archeological dig,
我就自己做了些调查
I started doing some digging of my own.
结果发现  几年前
Turns out, a few years ago,
在印度的挖掘现场  四个科学家身亡
four scientists were killed in an excavation in India
朱利安就是主要负责人
and Julian was the point person.
他从没提起过
He didn't mention that.
你说他痴迷于那个石头很多年了
You said he was obsessed with that stone for years.
如果他是在掩盖什么事呢
What if he was covering something up?
或者是什么人
Or someone?
你觉得这个和炼金术师有关吗
You think this is about Alchemy?
只有一个办法能找出结果来了
There's only one way to find out.
朱利安在魔法石的事上撒谎了
Julian lied about the Philosopher's Stone.
我觉得他在考古挖掘时找到了那块石头
I think he found it back on that archeological dig.
你觉得他在和炼金术博士合作吗
You think he's working with Doctor Alchemy?
他不接我电话
He's not answering my calls.
大家好啊
Hey, everyone.
大家都在啊  怎么了
Gang's all here, what's going on?
我觉得朱利安和炼金术博士有关
I think that Julian is connected to Doctor Alchemy.
舒尔茨大厦
杰伊  我们找到了
Jay, we got a hit.
舒尔茨大厦楼顶有能量释放
There's energy coming from the top of the Schults building.
-是魔法石  -准备好了吗
- That's the stone. - Are you ready?
-准备好了  -好的
- Ready. - All right.
我也去
I'm coming, too.
-你可不能去  -不行
- No you're not. - No.
爸  我准备好了
Dad, I'm ready.
你告诉他们我有多快
You--just tell them about how fast I am.
告诉他们训练的情况
Tell them about the training.
-训练  -训练
- Training? - Training?
训练啊  是声乐训练
Training. The vocal training.
因为我们想参加圣诞颂歌的合唱
Because we're thinking of going caroling.
我们之后再谈这个
We're gonna talk about this later.
我们绝对得好好谈谈
We're definitely gonna talk about it.
有了魔法石的能量
With energy form this stone,
有了这座楼当折射器
and this building as a refractor,
我将恢复闪点里所有超能力者的能力
I shall restore the powers of all the metas from Flashpoint.
他们将成为萨维塔的仆人
They will become the servants of Savitar.
都结束了  炼金术师
It's over, Alchemy!
快告诉我你看到他了
Please tell me you're seeing him.
我看到他了
I see him.
我们得合力击败他
We have to take him together.
不  我来拖住萨维塔
No, I'll cover Savitar,
你去拿魔法石
you just get that stone!
这不是你的战斗  加里克
This is not your fight, Garrick.
朱利安
Julian.
我在哪
Where am I?
发生了什么
What's going on?
这么说吧  你要在我们这里待一段时间了
Let's just say you're gonna be our guest for a while.
是你
You.
我一直怀疑你有关押敌人的
I always suspected you had your own private facility
秘密基地
for holding enemies.
你要解释一下我为什么在这里吗
You care to explain what I'm doing in it?
-我知道你是炼金术师  朱利安  -什么
- I know you're Alchemy, Julian. - What?
你把无辜的人变成超能力者
Turning innocent people into meta-humans,
膜拜那个萨维塔
worshipping this Savitar?
不好意思  我没听懂
Sorry, um, I'm still not following.
你觉得我是炼金术师吗
You think that I'm Alchemy?
这是我听过的最扯的话了
That's the most absurd thing I've ever heard.
那是面具吗
Is that a mask?
我这辈子都没见过那东西
I've never seen that before in my life.
我抓到你了
I caught you!
我抓到你戴着这个面具
I caught you wearing this mask.
你这是要陷害我
You're trying to set me up.
你要诬陷我  对不对
You're framing me, aren't you?
闪电侠  偏偏是你陷害我
The Flash, of all the people, you're setting me up.
-你还英雄呢  -你疯了
- The hero. - You're insane.
你个大英雄
The great hero!
我要打电话  我什么时候能打电话
I want my phone call, when do I get my phone call?
你怎么样
How you feeling?
对一个刚被神打了一顿的人来说
Not too bad for a guy
感觉还好吧
that got beat up by a myth.
-是吗  -你阻止了他
- Yeah? - You stopped him.
干的漂亮  巴里
Well done, Barry.
有你在我身边  感觉很好
It was nice, having you out there with me.
我以前都没有帮手
Yeah, I never had a sidekick.
-我是你的帮手啊  -作为一个长者搭档
- Oh, I'm your sidekick? - Well, as a senior partner.
长者市民还差不多
Senior citizen is more like it.
我打赌你爸爸一定会为你自豪的
I'll bet your dad would've been proud of you.
对吧
Right?
你还是好好休息下  好吗
Hey, why won't you just take it easy, all right?
-我一会儿来看你  -好
- I’ll see you in a little bit. - Yeah.
你对朱利安刚才说的话怎么看
What do you think about what Julian was saying?
我知道我们抓到的坏人
I know that every bad guy we've ever had
都装作是我们的好朋友  但实际上
has pretended to be our best friend, while really being
都是邪恶  杀人的混蛋  但是
an evil, murderous bastard, but...
我觉得如果他在撒谎
I think if he's lying,
他也真的太相信自己编的这个谎了
he sure believes the hell out of his own lie.
好了  这盒子到底怎么回事
Okay, well what do we think about this box?
相当恐怖
It's creepy.
跟《夺宝奇兵》里融掉你脸的圣柜似的
Like, "Indiana Jone" melt your face creepy.
你们弄清这是什么东西了吗
Have you guys figured out anything about it yet?
这什么都不是
It's nothing.
它肯定是个什么
It's something.
不  我是说这盒子真的什么都不是
No, I mean the box is literally nothing.
我把能想到的测试都做了一遍
I've run it through every possible test I can think of--
核磁共振  X光扫描  质谱仪  光子移动器
MRI, X-ray, mass spectrometer, the photon shifter.
什么都检测不到  毫无反应
Not a single reading. Nothing.
就好像这盒子
It's like the box
根本不存在
doesn't even exist.
两周前  炼金术师差点害我失去你
Two weeks ago, I almost lost you to Alchemy,
上周外星人也是
then last week aliens.
-我的心脏承受不住  沃利  -爸  他懂了
- My heart can't take it, Wally. - Dad, he gets it.
-爱瑞丝  他真懂吗  -我想他懂了
- Iris, does he? - I think so, yeah.
而你
And you...
几周之前  你还告诉我
A couple weeks ago. You were telling me
有多信任我和我的直觉
how you believed in me and my instincts,
现在却鼓励沃利来唱反调
and now you're encouraging Wally to do exactly the opposite?
我不知道他需要多少鼓励
I don't know how much encouraging he needed.
你这是怎么回事
What's the deal with you?
你是精神病吗  无论如何都要
You have some psychotic need to make other people like you
别人喜欢你吗
no matter what?
我想那不是精神病
I wouldn't call it psychotic.
我的问题是
No, my deal is,
我能慧眼识珠
I find people's true talents,
然后引导他们
and I just marshal them along.
你还有自己的想法吗
Do you even have your own opinions?
够了  别再责怪HR了
Stop. Stop banging on H.R.
都怪我  好吗
This was all me, okay?
我逼他训练我
I pushed him to train me.
我逼他帮我忙
I pushed him to help me.
反正也没有其他人愿意帮我
Wasn't like anyone else was lining up to do it.
怎么了
Hey. What's up?
是沃利的事
It's Wally.
我搞不懂  巴仔  他脑子浑浑噩噩的
I don't get it, Bar, it's like his brain goes to sleep
好像被别人掌控着
and somebody else is at the wheel.
你有忘记过时间  断片过吗
Have you been losing time? Blacking out?
时间流逝  醒来却身在异处
Hours passing, waking up somewhere different?
不知道怎么到了那里
Not being sure of how you got there.
-没有  -没有
- No. - No?
没有
No!
我受够这些毫无根据的指责
I've had enough of these baseless accusations
以及你这荒谬的理论
and ridiculous theories of yours.
朱利安  我想帮你
Julian, I'm trying to help you!
但你得信任我
But you need to trust me.
戴着面具谈什么信任
Says the man in a mask.
不  你说得对
No, you're right.
我早该知道的
I should've known.
我早该猜到了
I should've guessed it.
解释不通的缺席  痴迷于超能力者
The unexplained absences, your passion for metas.
对当局总是嗤之以鼻
Your general thumbing your nose at authority.
你肯定也在背后嘲笑死我了
I'm sure you had a good laugh behind my back.
我真想之前就告诉你了
I actually wished I could've told you before.
那现在为什么告诉我
So why tell me now?
因为我要你信任我  朱利安
Because I need you to trust me, Julian.
你是炼金术师
You are Alchemy.
我想你还没意识到这点
I just don't think you're aware of it.
现在  你有没有断片过
Now, have you been blacking out?
有
Yes.
什么时候开始的
When did it start?
我的妹妹  艾玛  在我20岁的时候去世了
My sister, Emma, died when I was 20.
这件事对我家打击真的很大
And it really broke the family up, you know?
爸爸妈妈都不说话
Mom and Dad weren't speaking,
他们甚至都不待在家里
they wouldn't even stay at the house.
有天晚上我一个人
One night, I was there alone,
然后她回来找我了
and she came back to me.
她就站在我面前
She stood right in front of me,
很清楚  我也分不清是鬼魂还是幻觉
clear as day--a ghost or a vision, I don't know,
但
but...
她很真实
she was real.
后来怎么了
What happened?
她告诉我有关魔法石的事
She told me about the stone.
她告诉我去哪能找到
She told me where to find it,
还说如果找到了
she told me that if I got it,
那就能让一家人再次团聚
then it would bring us back together again.
在那个时候
And at that point, mate,
我会不惜一切让她起死回生
I would've done anything to have her back.
所以我就这么做了
That's what I did.
我前往印度探险
I mounted an expedition to India.
我们搜寻了好几周
Days we searched, weeks.
一无所获
Nothing.
然后我们找到了
And then we found it.
后来我只记得在酒店客房里醒来
And the next thing I remember, I woke up in the hotel room.
我
I...
什么都不记得了
didn't remember anything,
从那以后就开始断片了
and that's when the blackouts started happening.
有个新闻报道说
There was a news report saying that
考古队里的其他人
every other member of my team had been found...
全都死在了发掘现场
dead at the site.
我慌了  我以为他们会怪罪到我头上
I panicked, I thought they were gonna blame me for their deaths,
于是我就逃走了
so I ran.
我逃到了美国
I ran to America.
你昏迷的时候会发生什么  朱利安
What happens when you black out, Julian?
是如何开始的
How does it start?
我听见一个声音
I hear the voice.
西斯科
Cisco.
你这是要失去理智了
You're losing it, man,
要失去理智了
you're losing it.
别再来吓我了
Stop scaring me!
不管你是什么东西  这样不好
Whatever you are, it's not cool, okay?
我知道你是什么东西
I know exactly what you are.
你是我过度悲伤所产生的臆想
You are a figment of my grief.
请你快消失吧
Please just leave.
这不可能  西斯科
I can't do that, Cisco.
这不是真的
This is not real.
我要吃点抗精神病药  凯特琳
Okay, I need an anti-psychotic. Caitlin!
如果你走了
If you leave,
那我也要走了
I'm gonna have to leave, too.
所以你是说我...
So you're telling me that -- that
每次我昏迷过去...
every time I'm blacking out...
你就化身成了炼金术师
You've become Alchemy.
这不可能
That's impossible.
炼金术师就是个怪物
Alchemy is a monster,
他这几年一直都在恐吓着市民
he's been terrorizing people for years.
听着  这些不是真正的你做的
Look, it's not you.
就像挖掘现场那事也不是你做的
Just like it wasn't you back on that dig.
我知道这很难让人相信
I know that this is hard to believe,
但你不得不接受发生在你身上的现实
but you have to start accepting what's happening to you.
你难道不想我们团聚吗
Don't you want us to be together again?
这个魔法石
The stone.
是一切的关键
It's the key to everything.
它可以转化人类
It can transform people.
打开它  我就能获得重生
Open it and I can be reborn.
我们就可以团聚了
We can be together again.
我们可以一起把那瓶威士忌喝了
We can have that bottle of whiskey.
毕竟  今天是圣诞节啊  兄弟
After all, it is Christmas, hermano.
是充满奇迹的时刻
It's the time of miracles.
我好想你是真的
I just want this to be real.
把盒子打开就行了
Just open the box.
我爱你  西斯科
I love you, Cisco.
丹堤
Dante.
Dante?
发生什么了
What's that?
-伙计们  什么情况  -西斯科的工作室
- Guys, what's going on? - Cisco's workshop.
巴里  他把盒子打开了
Barry, he opened the box.
等等
Wait.
西斯科
Cisco?
跪拜你的神
Bow to your god.
发生什么了
What is happening?
我们看不见它
We can't see it,
就像在炼金术师巢穴那里一样
just like at Alchemy's lair.
萨维塔逃出来了
Savitar's loose.
杰伊  杰伊  你的重伤还没好
Hey, Jay, Jay, you're still too badly hurt.
记住  躲闪迂回
Remember: dodge and weave.
沃利  别去
Wally, no!
我能看见他
I can see him.
好极了  吸引他的注意
Great. Get his attention.
你这个金属怪
Yo, metal mouth.
显然没人教你怎么和人和睦相处
Clearly, nobody taught you how to play nice with others.
西斯科  你必须把盒子关上
Cisco? Cisco, you have to close the box!
我要救丹提
I'm gonna save Dante.
那不是丹提  那是萨维塔
It's -- that's not Dante, it's Savitar.
他是在利用你的回忆来操纵你
Please, he's using your memories against you!
你是个好弟弟  西斯科
You're a good brother, Cisco.
西斯科  我们没有时间了
Cisco, we're running out of time.
快把盒子给我
Please, just hand me the box.
我不会再一次失去他了
I won't lose him again.
我不会再一次失去我哥哥了
I will not lose my brother again!
西斯科  丹提已经去世了
Cisco, Dante is gone.
我很抱歉  可是人死不能复生
I'm so sorry, but there is nothing you can do about it.
但是你现在有机会可以救另外的人
But there are people you can save right now.
如果你不赶快把盒子关上
If you don't close that box,
巴里和沃利会死的
Barry and Wally will die.
如果你关上了  我们就不能在一起了
If you do, we can't be together.
西斯科  听我话
Cisco, listen to me!
不要
Don't.
对不起  哥哥
Lo siento, hermano.
谢了
Thanks.
开什么玩笑  刚才太刺激了
You kidding? That was awesome.
你确定你没事吗
Are you sure you're okay?
目前完整无缺
Still in one piece.
我不知道发生了什么
I don't know what happened.
所以现在盒子关上了
So now that the box is closed,
萨维塔就彻底消失了吗
Savitar's, what, gone for good?
我不知道  但是我们要查清楚
I don't know, but we need to find out.
西斯科
Cisco?
如果我们不能利用这个盒子
If we can't use this box,
朱利安或许是现在我们和萨维塔
Julian, he may be our only link
唯一的联系了  对吗
to Savitar now, right?
我觉得两者我们都能用上
I think we can use both of them.
如果凯特琳说得没错
If Caitlin's right and this thing
这东西能扰乱脑电波  那我有办法了
messes with brainwaves,then I have a plan.
你又让我儿子陷入险境
You put my son's life in danger again.
但是他救了巴里的命
And he saved Barry's life.
乔  为什么
Joe, why...
你觉得为什么我要帮沃利
why do you think I help Wally?
因为我自私  要什么好处吗
'Cause I'm selfish, I get something--
我没得到任何好处
I don't get anything out of it.
我帮沃利是因为这孩子很特别
I help Wally 'cause the kid is special.
他和常人不同
He's extraordinary.
他的超能力非同凡响  听着  我明白了
His powers are extraordinary and--look, I get it.
我不是他老爸  我不像你
I'm--I'm not his dad and I don't have the same
那么担心他的安危  这是当然
safety concerns as you, of course not,
但是乔  我很确信一件事
but Joe, one thing I do know,
你越是不承认一个人的潜力
the longer you deny someone their potential,
他们就越想从别处得到认同
the more they're gonna look for it elsewhere.
要我到这里来干什么
So what am I doing here?
朱利安  今天我和萨维塔打斗时
Okay, Julian, today when I was fighting Savitar,
他和炼金术师的声音是一样的
it--he and Alchemy, they had the same voice.
好吧  那是什么意思
All right, what does that mean?
我觉得炼金术师并不存在
I don't think there is an Alchemy,
我觉得是萨维塔通过你和我们对话
I think it's Savitar speaking through you.
明显是萨维塔控制了有信徒追随的人
Savitar clearly possesses someone who rallies worshippers.
但他就像吵闹鬼  要借助他人现真身
But he's like a poltergeist, he needs a medium to manifest himself.
就是你
You.
好吧  但这说明什么
Right, but what does that mean?
我们想出了一个办法
We think we figured out a way
让你的大脑和魔法石同步
to sync your brain to the stone.
这样我们就能直接和萨维塔对话了
And it'll allow us to speak directly to Savitar.
我觉得...
I thought--
如果你想摆脱这个
If you want to try to be free of this,
你就得信任我们
you need to trust us.
我一直都不喜欢你  艾伦
I've never liked you, Allen.
是啊
Yeah.
和你的朋友搞降神会
Having a little séance with your friends now
也不能改变事实
is not gonna help change that fact.
你是知道的
You do know that.
好吧  我试试
Fine, I'll try it.
深呼吸
Deep breaths.
-可以吗  -可以
- Okay? - Yeah.
你要从十开始倒数
You're gonna count backwards from ten.
十...
Te--
这么快
That was quick.
好了  那这要等多久才起作用
Okay, so, um, how long till this works?
不是很确定  脑电波可能要几分钟...
Not really sure, it may take a minute for his brain waves--
你好  巴里
Hello, Barry.
好久不见
It's been a while.
萨维塔
Savitar?
你们都没对我下跪
None of you are on your knees.
在神灵面前应该鞠躬示敬
It's a smart move to bow before a deity.
你不是神灵
You're not God.
想当神  你只需要让人们
To be a god, you just have to make people
相信你就是
believe you are.
没有人相信你
No one believes in you.
你该信的  爱瑞丝
You should, Iris.
我掌控了你们的生死大权
I hold the power of life and death over all of you.
你怎么如此了解我们
How do you know so much about us?
我认识你  凯特琳
I know you, Caitlin.
西斯科  乔  沃利
Cisco, Joe, Wally.
假威尔斯
The fake Wells.
我了解你们的恐惧和弱点
I know your fears and I know your weaknesses.
我比你们自己更了解你们
I know you better than you know yourselves.
我知道你们的宿命
I know your destinies.
有个人会背叛
One shall betray you.
有个人会堕落
One shall fall.
有个人会遭遇比死还悲惨的命运
One will suffer a fate far worse than death.
这就是我对你们的了解
This is the knowledge I have for you.
还有对你们永恒的诅咒
About your everlasting damnation.
你是谁
Who are you?
我就是未来的闪电侠
I am the future, Flash.
你想从我们这得到什么
What do you want from us?
一切
Everything!
我要讨回你们夺走我的一切
Everything you took from me, I want it back.
而我也一定会夺回来
And I'm gonna take it back.
然后我会摧毁你们
Then, I will destroy you.
那你为什么还不动手
Then why haven't you already?
如果你真的无所不能  你为什么不
If you're all-powerful, then why don't you just
直接把我们杀了  了结一切呢
go ahead and kill us all now, be done with it?
因为你不能
Because you can't.
我这样都是拜你所赐
You did this to me.
你把我困在了永恒之中
You trapped me in eternity.
未来的你把我害成这样  巴里
Your future self-- you did this to me, Barry.
现在该我复仇的时候了
And now the age of my revenge rises.
我的自由近在眼前
My freedom is at hand.
你们将感受我的愤怒
You will feel my wrath.
萨维塔的愤怒
The wrath of Savitar!
成功了吗
Did it work?
真太吓人了
That was so scary.
我是说  这还不够可怕吗
I mean, that was-- was it not truly frightening,
那个声音  那个预言  还有...
what the voice and the prophesies and the--
简直是一次惊悚马拉松  不是吗
it was--I mean, that a scare-a-thon, wasn't it?
我得喝点薄荷茶和咖啡  然后再躺会
I'm gonna have a mint tea and a coffee and a lay down.
你们觉得他说的  我们其中
Do you think the things that he said about
有个人背叛他  还有个人会死
one of us betraying him and one of us dying
可能是真的吗
could really be true?
如果真是未来的巴里
I mean, if it really was future Barry
惹怒了他并把他关在某处
that pissed him off and locked him up somewhere,
那或许他知道未来我们发生了什么
then maybe he knows what happens to future us.
他不知道
He doesn't.
他永远不会逃出禁锢的
He's never getting out of wherever he's trapped.
那我们要如何阻止他
So how are we supposed to stop him?
魔法石
The stone.
杰伊是对的  魔法石是一切的关键
Jay's right, the stone has been the key to everything.
他就是这样控制了朱利安
It's--it's how he controlled Julian,
还制造了更多超能力者
it's how he's created more metas.
所以只要毁掉魔法石  萨维塔就会永远消失
So we destroy the stone and Savitar is gone for good.
不可能毁掉的
It's impossible to destroy.
它存在这么久了  肯定是有原因
It's been around forever, there's a reason for that.
我们何不把它埋起来
Why don't we just bury it again,
放回你当初发现它的地方
put it back in the ground where you found it?
《勇敢者的游戏》
"Jumanji"
别人还会找到它  我们的努力就
Someone would just find it and we'd be right back
前功尽弃了
where we started.
我们要让那个盒子永远消失
We need to make that box disappear forever.
我们只有一个办法
There's only one thing we can do with it.
把它扔进神速力里
Throw it into the Speed Force.
-慢着  你能做到  -没错
- Wait, you can do that? - Oh, yeah.
神速力本身就是永恒的
The Speed Force is eternity itself,
时间与能量组成的无尽真空
an endless void of time and energy.
那样好比把它扔进了太空  无处可寻
It'd be like trying to find it after it got lost in space.
但那块石头充满了重力  我是说
But that stone is loaded with gravimetric force.I mean,
我觉得你带着它的同时
I don't think you could run fast enough
无法跑得足够快  以让你进入神速力
to reach the Speed Force and carry that at the same time.
有我的帮助就行
He can with my help.
我们以最快速度奔跑
We run as fast as we can.
你在我后面  吸收一些我的速度
You trail behind me, siphon off some of my speed,
与自己的速度结合  等你有足够速度时
combine it with your own, and when you have enough,
把那东西扔进神速力深处
throw that thing deep into the Speed Force.
这办法可行吗
And that would work?
让我们试试看
We need to find out.
你准备好了吗  闪电侠
Sure you're up for this, Flash?
没问题  闪电侠
You got it, Flash.
达到最佳速度时我会告诉你
I'll let you know when you reach optimal speed.
好的
All right.
预备  跑
Ready...go!
杰伊跑得真快  这办法也许行得通
Jay's moving really fast, this might actually work.
趁现在  巴里
Now, Barry!
据另一条法律新闻  杰拉德·莫里罗
In other legal news, the highly publicized trial
因凡蒂诺街
即"掠夺"  备受瞩目的审讯已经结束
of Jared Morillo, AKA "Plunder," comes to a close.
今年初  莫里罗
Morillo was found guilty of grand theft
在抢劫中城博物馆时被闪电侠抓获
and aggravated assault after he was caught by the Flash
他因重大盗窃和故意伤害被判有罪
robbing the Central City Museum earlier this year.
不要
Don't!
请不要
Please don't!
不要这么做
Don't do this.
现在  我终于摆脱你的禁锢了
Now, finally, I am free of you.
巴里  我爱你
Barry, I love you.
不  别说这话  知道吗
No, don't say that, all right?
你不会有事的
You're gonna be all right.
-我乞求你不要  -巴里
- I'm begging you, just-- - Barry!
你输了  巴里
You lose, Barry.
不
No!
爱瑞丝  爱瑞丝  醒醒
Iris. Iris, hey...
不  爱瑞丝
No. Iris.
爱瑞丝  爱瑞丝
Iris, Iris...
杰伊
Jay?
刚是什么情况  我那是在哪
What the hell was that? Where was I?
在未来
The future.
我从没跑进过未来
I've never run to the future.
我试过回到过去
I've traveled to the past,
但我总能返回到现在
but I always came back to the present.
我看到了我自己
I saw myself.
还有爱瑞丝  还有...
And Iris. And
萨维塔  他...
Savitar, what--
他杀了她
he killed her.
是五个月之后的事
That's five months from now.
那真的会发生吗
Is that actually gonna happen?
-我不知道  -你不知...
- I don't know. - You don't--
你不应该看到那些
You shouldn't have seen that.
这完全说不通  我们...
This doesn't make sense, we--
我们刚扔掉了魔法石
we just got rid of the Philosopher's Stone.
萨维塔不该在那儿
I mean, Savitar shouldn't have even been there!
我的天
Oh, my God.
所以时间穹顶里的报纸变了
This is where the newspaper in the time vault changed.
署名变了  所以不是爱瑞丝
The byline, this is why it's not Iris, this...
八年后不再是爱瑞丝
Iris didn't write that story anymore
写那篇报道  因为
eight years from now, because...
她死了
she's dead.
巴里
Barry...
我眼睁睁地看着她死
I just watched her die.
我看到我试图救她  但是我不够快
I saw myself try to save her, but I wasn't fast enough.
杰伊  告诉我这不是我的命运
Jay, tell me that this isn't my destiny.
你看到的是未来的一种可能
What you saw was one possibility of the future.
也许是这样  也许不是
What may be, or what may not.
那么我可以阻止它发生了吗
Okay, then I can stop this from happening.
-我可以回到那儿  -你不能回去
- I can run back there-- - You can't go back there.
不能再去  永远不能
Not again, not ever.
好  我会弄清楚到底是怎么发生的
All right, then I'll figure out exactly how it happened,
怎么会最后在街上
how we wind up on that street,
我会确保我们不去那里
and I'll just make sure that we don't go there.
-如果我们不去  -巴里
- And if we don't go there-- - Barry!
这就是极速者不穿越到未来的原因
This is why speedsters don't travel to the future.
没人该知道自己未来这么多事
Nobody should know this much about their own.
就像多元宇宙中有无数地球一样
Just as their are infinite Earths in the multiverse,
未来也有无数种可能性
there are infinite possibilities to the future.
总是在扭曲  总是在变化
It's always bending, always changing.
你做的每一个决定衍生出另一种可能
Every decision you make creates another alternative.
我不会让爱瑞丝死的
I won't let Iris die.
未来还没有定下来
The future isn't written yet.
也许并不是你看到的那样
And it might not even turn out to be what you saw.
你要着眼于当下
You need to focus on the here and now.
要过好你的生活
You have to live your life.
-伙计们  -嗨
- Hey, guys. - Hey.
你还好吗  你和杰伊消失了
Are you okay? You and Jay disappeared, and...
我还好
Naw, I'm okay.
-只是见到你很开心  -杰伊在哪
- I'm just glad to see you. - So where's Jay?
杰伊打算继续跑回到地球三
Jay, uh, decided to go ahead and go back to Earth-3.
他祝大家圣诞快乐
But he wanted to wish everybody a Merry Christmas.
起作用了吗  魔法石...
So, it worked? The stone...
消失了
It's gone.
-消失在神速力中了  -很好
- It's lost in the Speed Force. - Good, good.
我不知道你们怎么想  但是想到
I don't know about you guys, but being mind-punked
我们未来惹恼了极速之神
by a speed god that we piss off in the future,
足以破坏过圣诞节的气氛
it's--it's enough to kill your Christmas spirit.
伙计们  圣诞节到了
Guys, Christmastime is here.
此时此刻我们需要
We need a little Christmas.
一点圣诞氛围  有人同意吗
Right this very minute. Who's with me?
-BA  -他说得对
- BA. - Well, he's right.
圣诞节我们应该一起过
It's Christmas, we should be together.
来过节吧
Let's have it.
其他人要过我也过
I'm still in if everybody else is.
-棒  -好  我们会去的
- Yes! - Okay, we'll be there.
棒
Yeah!
朱利安
Julian...
他要去哪
Where's he going?
你要去哪
Hey, where ya going?
你圣诞节有计划吗
Do you have Christmas plans?
韦斯特一家要开圣诞节聚会
The West's are having a Christmas get-together.
经过这些事后你不应该一个人呆着
After what you've been through, you shouldn't be alone.
实际上我更想一个人过圣诞节
I actually prefer to be alone at Christmas.
雨中过圣诞
Rain on Christmas.
既不神圣又不愉快
That's neither holy nor jolly.
我想说
Hey, listen, um...
丹堤的事情
about Dante.
谢谢你帮我解开心结
Thank you for talking me off the ledge.
不客气  你也会为我做同样的事
Of course, you'd do the same for me.
事实上  你为我做过
In fact, you did the same for me.
我正想说
I was gonna say.
凯特科  西斯琳
Caitlo--Caitlo, Ciscan...
你们得尝尝这蛋酒
okay--whoo-- you got to try the eggnog
乔和他的火辣女友
a holiday concoction done by Joe
做的节日混合酒
and his hot girlfriend...
宝贝
Babe.
-怎么了  -没什么
- What's up? - Nothing.
你看起来有些奇怪  不是吗
You seem a little weird. No?
你知道我们赢了吧
You do know we won, right?
我们打败了坏人
We defeated the bad guy.
-是  我知道  -好的
- Yeah, I know. - Okay.
-埃丝特祖母  -米莉祖母
- Grandma Esther. - Grandma Millie.
试试看
Let's see.
天  酒真烈
Damn, that's strong.
这杯也是  我天
So is that, my God!
我们的祖母都是酒鬼
Our grandmothers are alcoholics.
没错
Yes.
严格来说  我们不是必须要
You know, technically, we don't have to be standing
站在槲寄生下
under the mistletoe to-- mm.
终于
Finally.
不需要小屁孩指指点点
No comments from the peanut gallery.
没有  但真的是时候了
No, but really, it's about time.
等一下
Hold on.
是我女儿
And it's my daughter.
等我一下
ah, just give me a quick minute,
我马上回来跟你继续
and then we can--yeah.
-宝贝  -乔
- Hey, kiddo... - Joe.
我看见你吻她了  干得好
I saw you kiss her, good job.
我们...没错  就是那样
We're--oh, that's right, the thing.
BA  过来
BA, hey. Come on.
你吃了多少那个了
How many of those have you had?
-你去哪了  -我在这里
- B--where'd you go? Here. - I'm right here.
我看见了
Oh, I see ya.
现在塞西尔走开了
Now that Cecile's away,
这是我们一起送你的
this is from all of us to you.
圣诞快乐  儿子
Merry Christmas, son.
-真的吗  -对呀  现在是时候了
- Are you serious? - Yeah, man, it's time.
你准备好了 华莱士
You're ready, Wallace.
欢迎你加入队伍
Welcome to the team.
闪电小子
Kid Flash.
真的要叫我闪电小子吗
Are we really calling me "Kid Flash"?
我想是的
Yeah, I think we are.
闪电小子
Kid Flash!
-警察  -我来
- Police! - I got it.
不是警察  我们是警察
It's not the police. We're the police.
你是警察
You're the police!
冷静
Calm down.
你好  朱利安
Hey, Julian.
-进来吧  我来  -谢谢
- Come on in. Here, let me get that. - Thanks.
发生了这么多事后
after everything that happened,
感觉孤军奋战挺寂寞的
being alone felt a bit lonely, so...
这是给你的
This is for you.
这是什么
What's this?
我跟辛格队长谈过了  他还没
I spoke to Captain Singh, and he hadn't put through
处理你的辞职申请
your resignation paperwork yet, so...
如果你想回到你以前的实验室
well, if you'd, uh, you know, like your old lab back,
或者你想跟我继续一起合用
or you'd like to share it again.
谢谢你  朱利安
Thanks, Julian.
圣诞快乐  伙计
Merry Christmas, man.
-谢谢你  伙计  -谢谢你
- Cheers, mate. - Yeah, thank you.
-圣诞快乐  -圣诞快乐
- Merry Christmas. - Merry Christmas.
-你要蛋酒吗  -好啊
- Can I offer you some eggnog? - I'd love some, yeah.
大家圣诞快乐
Happy Christmas, everyone
很高兴你来了
I'm glad you came.
谢谢你
Thank you, yeah.
-听见了吗  -在外面
- Do you hear that? - It's outside.
报佳音
Carolers.
雨中报佳音
Caroling in the rain.
真糟糕
That sucks.
-你在干什么  -没事  我可以
- What're you doing? - It's okay, I got this.
虽然我们无法过个完美的圣诞
We may not be able to have a perfect Christmas,
但我们能过个白色圣诞
but we can have a white one.
那么
So.
我们什么时候交换礼物
When are we gonna exchange presents?
现在就交换吧
How 'bout right now?
-好  -跟我走
- Okay. - Follow me.
-好  -我们走吧
- Okay. - Let's get out of here.
小心门槛
Okay, going through a door, be careful.
好  我到了
Okay, right here.
-准备好了吗  -好了
- Okay, are you ready? - Yeah.
好
All right.
现在可以睁开
Open your eyes...
眼睛
now.
我不明白  这是哪里
I--I don't understand, where are we?
家
Home.
什么
What?
我不能再睡在西斯科的沙发了
I couldn't sleep on Cisco's couch anymore,and
你那里又不够两个人住
your place is sort of small for two,
所以我租下了这里
so I signed a lease
放了我俩的名字
and I put both of our names on it.
我只给你买了个钱包
I got you a wallet.
我肯定会很喜欢
I'm sure I'll love it.
巴里  你跨出了一大步
Barry, this is a big step.
我不觉得
Not for me.
我不知道未来会怎样
I don't know what's gonna happen in the future.
我只知道此时此地
All I know is, right here, right now,
我要跟你一起度过所有时光
I want to spend every moment I can with you.
你是我每天醒来要见到的第一个人
You're the first thing I want to see when I wake up.
还有睡前
And the last thing--
我爱你  巴里·艾伦
I love you, Barry Allen.
我爱你  爱瑞丝·韦斯特
I love you, Iris West.